americommerce.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Policy

AmeriCommerce is committed to privacy and security for all of our clients. Because we respect your right to privacy, we have developed a Privacy Statement as indicated below.

## Personal Information  

**Under no circumstances do we transfer your email address to any other company** , nor do we collect any personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs. 

There are two ways you can provide us with and consent to our collection of certain personal information:

**E-mail Request** \- Links throughout our site provide you with the opportunity to contact us via e-mail to ask questions, request information and materials, or provide comments and suggestions. You may also be offered the opportunity to have one of our Sales Representatives contact you personally to provide additional information about our products or services. To do so, we may request additional personal information from you, such as your name and telephone number, to help us satisfy your request. 

**Enrollment** – You may choose to enroll for one of our products or services, we will request certain information from you. Depending on the type of product or service that you request, you may be asked to provide different personal information. For certain products and services, we may require your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number. Other products and services may require different or supplemental information from you in order to apply. 

## Statistical Information About Your Visit  

Information obtained while visiting our site does not identify you personally, but rather about a visit to our site. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our site, which pages people visit, and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit to help us improve the performance of our Web site. 

## Your Ability to Opt-Out of Further Notifications  

Periodically, we notify our customers of new products, announcements, and updates. If you would like to opt-out of being notified, please contact us at info@americommerce.com.
